SACHIN ATAL

BRAND MANAGER (ANIMATION)

As someone who can identify the need of customers for effective solutions, Make strategy on the bases of companies ROI. I'm committed to high-quality service that ensures a positive experience.

PERSONALITY HIGHLIGHTS

- Cheerful disposition
- · Neat and well-organized
- Motivated by problem solving
- Independent worker
- Team management skills
- Collaborative and efficient

CONTACT DETAILS

726-C Paschim puri, Pocket 2 New Delhi, 110063

Sachinatal2@gmail.com

9971732071

BASIC INFORMATION

I am a professional Brand Strategist / Manager with over 7 years experience in handling all marketing terms and business. My unique professional experience stems from years of providing excellent customer support, creative problem solving and building customer loyalty. To obtain a position that will allow me to utilize my strategic skills, experience and willingness to learn in making an organisation successful

EDUCATION

Delhi University Graduate in B. Com
Institute of cost and management accountant ICMA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Teleone Pvt Ltd / Maha Cartoon Tv Brand Manager August 2019 - Present

- Leadership role for Maha Cartoon Tv Teams (over 100 employees) and execution of operational strategy
- Taking care of all Revenue and expenses responsibility of the firm Including Income, Salary of Staff, Building, Maintenance and other expenses.
- Maintain Profit and Loss statements, budgets, and cost controls in regard to Cartoon Stories, movies and different kind of videos
- Creating and maintaining a work environment conducive to teamwork, creativity, quality, operational efficiency, and value acceleration
- Develop productive relationships with sponsors;
 market intellectual property of the Department
- Analyzed and maintain all platforms in Digital Marketing, Animation, to increase the company's performance User behavior and keywords ranking with using different type of tools.

Hitech institute of advance technology

Digital Head / Strategist July 2018- July 2019

- Evaluated client websites for mobile performance and optimal search engine ranking.
- Analyse the Business tactics to identify new flexibility in the market
- Analyzed website, User behavior and keywords ranking with using tools like google analytics, webmaster, Arhrefs & Similarweb.com
- Own and manage a handsome PPC budget to achieve pre-agreed channel targets

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Because of my strong impersonal & strategic skills, Selected as a assistant manager in marketing by monster jobs in the same year.
- Got a Chance to shoot the scene of movie BHAG MILKHA BHAG
- Work with ANURAG KASHYAP for the movie BHAVESH JOSHI

PERSONAL DETAILS

• DATE OF BIRTH : 24/03/1994

• MARITAL STATUS : SINGLE

• NATIONALITY : INDIAN

- KNOWN LANGUAGES : ENGLISH & HINDI
- HOBBY : READING BOOKS MARKETING STRATEGY AND RESEARCH

- Develop the social media strategy, Email strategy as well as SMS marketing and carried out for the two brands under the parent brand using tools like mail-chimp, Webster, Fast SMS, Buffer and Canva.
- Generate and refine keywords and ad copy; create and manage RLSA segmentation and activity
- Utilize financial data and analysis in strategic decision making to meet company's ROI and budget requirements
- Manage the team of marketing professionals to ensure the success of marketing campaigns.

Kaya.in

Marketing strategist/ Business analyst Dec 2017 - May 2018

- Conducted market research and initiated business development for an international cosmetic product company
- List companies product in different platforms like amazon, nykaa, flipkart and increase the companies revenue by 18%.
- Create brand reputation campaign that allow our customers to nock our online door through the Ecommerce market place.
- Increased conversion rates, reduced bounce rates, and improved ROI by monitoring analytics reports and adjust accordingly

Mount Wolf Entertainments

Managing director
Mar 2014 - Nov 2017

- Build own firm of events, production house as well as modelling agency.
- Event management and production house deals in media, events and movie projects
- Ultimately responsible for all day-to-day management decisions for implement the company's long and short term plan..
- Managed team and all event activities.

Monster jobs

Assistant Manager(Marketing) Jan 2013 - Dec 2014

- Assist marketing head with strategy execution and marketing research.
- Organized Digital marketing campaign and events.
- Execute team with innovation on different projects
 Managed team and all event activities
- Provide administrative support to the marketing department